export const questions2 = [
  { id: 1, type: 'mc', question: 'Which pandemic is the deadliest in modern history', options: ['A. The bubonic plague in the 14th century', 'B. The Covid-19 coronavirus in 2020', 'C. The Philadelphia yellow fever epidemic in 1793', 'D. The Spanish Flu in 1918'], answer: 'D. The Spanish Flu in 1918' },
  { id: 2, type: 'mc', question: 'The Spanish Flu pandemic occurred during which war?', options: ['A. World War I', 'B. The French Revolution', 'C. The Spanish-American War', 'D. World War II'], answer: 'A. World War I' },
  { id: 3, type: 'mc', question: 'Where did the Spanish flu originate?', options: ['A. Italy', 'B. Spain', 'C. United States', 'D. That information is not provided'], answer: 'D. That information is not provided' },
  { id: 4, type: 'mc', question: 'Why are total deaths for the Spanish Flu not known?', options: ['A. Many areas did not keep medical records', 'B. Most medical records were destroyed in the war', 'C. No one wants to know how bad it was', 'D. No one cared because of the war'], answer: 'A. Many areas did not keep medical records' },
  { id: 5, type: 'mc', question: 'When was the first wave of the Spanish Flu pandemic?', options: ['A. Summer 1918', 'B. Spring 1918', 'C. Fall 1918', 'D. Winter 1918'], answer: 'B. Spring 1918' },
  { id: 6, type: 'mc', question: 'What contributed to deaths from the flu in military personnel?', options: ['A. Unsanitary conditions', 'B. Poor nutrition', 'C. All of the above', 'D. Close quarters'], answer: 'C. All of the above' },
  { id: 7, type: 'mc', question: 'What is a characteristic feature of serious cases of the Spanish Flu?', options: ['A. Face turning blue', 'B. Extremely high fever', 'C. Coma', 'D. Liver failure'], answer: 'A. Face turning blue' },
  { id: 8, type: 'mc', question: 'What caused the Spanish Flu pandemic to end?', options: ['A. Those who were susceptible had either died or were immune', 'B. They created a vaccine for it', 'C. The end of the war caused better conditions', 'D. Improved medical care'], answer: 'A. Those who were susceptible had either died or were immune' },
  { id: 9, type: 'mc', question: 'When did John travel to Las Vegas?', options: ['A. Last summer', 'B. Last spring', 'C. Yesterday', 'D. Last weekend'], answer: 'B. Last spring' },
  { id: 10, type: 'mc', question: 'What is an activity that a tourist cannot do on The Strip?', options: ['A. Visit the Grand Canyon', 'B. Shop', 'C. Eat', 'D. Stay overnight'], answer: 'A. Visit the Grand Canyon' },
  { id: 11, type: 'mc', question: 'Which best describes the purpose of the Las Vegas Strip?', options: ['A. It offers a lot of activities for tourists.', 'B. It keeps tourists safe.', 'C. It is a 2.5 mile stretch.', 'D. There are too many neon lights.'], answer: 'A. It offers a lot of activities for tourists.' },
  { id: 12, type: 'mc', question: 'Explain why John liked his visit to the Grand Canyon.', options: ['A. It is one of the Seven Natural Wonders of the World.', 'B. John does not enjoy spending time in cities.', 'C. The Grand Canyon offers a breathtaking view.', 'D. The setting was very different from downtown Las Vegas.'], answer: 'D. The setting was very different from downtown Las Vegas.' },
  { id: 13, type: 'mc', question: 'What does it mean that Las Vegas is a “city that never sleeps?”', options: ['A. There is too much noise here for people to sleep.', 'B. A lot of people here have sleep disorders.', 'C. The neon lights keep people awake at night.', 'D. Las Vegas offers exciting activities at all hours.'], answer: 'D. Las Vegas offers exciting activities at all hours.' },
  { id: 14, type: 'mc', question: 'Predictions made twenty years ago that the phonograph record was about to become obsolete have proven to be true. Is the sentence “predictions made twenty years ago” properly constructed or not?', options: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'], answer: 'B' },
  { id: 15, type: 'mc', question: 'Walking by the corner the other day,_______________for the light to change. The sentence is incomplete. To correctly fix the sentence, choose from the following answers.', options: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'], answer: 'C' },

];